So another new day and another new beginning and
today we are going to Royal Enfield service
centre and the purpose of going there is that our
Hunter had an accident and its
handle etc. got bent, so I have made an
insurance claim, so now let us see what is the
process of insurance, what is it, what is it not, I will
tell you like that, now brother, move aside a bit,
you will also see, I will also see and let us see whether
I get the insurance or not.
By the way, my insurance was
from this company ICICIC Lambor, first
party and it is also for 5 years, so the one which is for 5
years is third party and the other one is
first party,
so right now I have gone to the service centre
and another bike of mine is going
which is being driven by my friend,
as you can see here,
this lever is completely bent and it is
not able to pump due to which the
front braking is also not effective.
You can see that it got scratched from here, the
whole thing got scratched here as well.  There was a scratch here too
and the biggest major
impact came here, and this too was
saved by the Lake Guard.  But I
feel that its handle T etc. has also become a
little bent and
its handle has come a little to this side
due to which this position is not getting upright.
So let's see if the
claim has been filed in the insurance.  Now they will
check whether they get insurance or not.  Everything else
is fine.  There are just some handling issues here and there.
So let's go now and
enjoy the ride.   It is a
completely uncomfortable position because it has
come to this side.  Due to which there
is a lot of problem.  Come on brother, this is our friend
and I am taking him along so that if
I have to surrender
this Hunter bike there, then I can
come with him on this bike.  So both the bikes are going
our way.  Let me show you what the
insurance claim process is like?
What is it and you will also get to know
that how is the insurance of ICICI Lamborgh
and if I had invested money in it
and given that money to the company then
what kind of service is it providing me.  Well, it has been at
least a week since I had these accidents.
But the thought of insurance
came to me later that yes, I have taken
insurance.  So I will make a claim in the insurance.
Because these small
things like this handle band,
I could have got it done at my own expense.   But
we take insurance.  So the
meaning of insurance is that
if you have given money to the company, then
what benefits is the company giving you according to that
and how quickly the claims are getting settled
and whether there will be any tantrums
in the claim, then I want to experience that thing.
So I will also experience it.   I
will get it done for you too and you will also see it and I
will also see it.  Well, I was in the right position.   It
ran perfectly fine, leaving the handle completely unattended.
But now it's slightly on this side.
So I have to drive it without holding it.  The
handle is moving like this.
Well, I will not drive it that much because it has an
issue with its handle.  So, the only major issue is that
I feel that if its
handle bar is changed then almost the
problem will be solved.  But if the issue
comes out of its tongs then it will cost a lot.
And brother, let's see what happens.  That's why
I have included it in the insurance claim.
Well, it's 11:11 now.  It's afternoon time.  There
is some sunshine and this sunshine
is fine right now but in the afternoon it will become very
hot.  So right now the nearest
service center for me is
in Fatehpur, which is
nearest to me among Sultanpur Mehrauli, so that is why
I am
preferring it right now.  I will
go there now and see what is the process there for
claiming this thing because the surveyor has
called me personally.  He
said that you should go and submit it once.
After submission, we
will send your surveyor and then tell you
how much claim can be made under it
and how much it will cost you.  I
also said okay okay, it was
not a big deal to get it changed, it would have been more like
changing the handle wire, I could have got it done at my own expense, but
if there is a
problem with the tongs near the bottom, with its lower body,
then it is a big problem because then
it would cost a lot, so
when I have taken insurance from the company, then
why should I pay extra, let's see
what benefits the company gives us, so now we are about to
reach our service center, in between
I have to switch the camera
because I have to shoot for mini vlogs as well
and I have to shoot for this also,
for YouTube, so there is a
little problem but but let's do it, it is okay, I have to do it
for the content, so the
distance is not much left,
just one to two km more distance, from
here I have to cut left,
then after that we reach our
destination and after going there we will see what the
claim process is or is not, whatever it is.  I will
update you in this vlog
and will also make a small short video
for you about how
easy and hassle free the claim process is.
Because I have already completed half the process online.  The
advantage of doing it online is
that you have everything at your disposal.
You will just have a surveyor waiting there.
You have to show it to the surveyor there.  The
surveyor will give approval and everything will be done for you.  So
far, that's what I'm thinking.  Let us see
what the process is going to be next.  How critical it is, how
easy it is.  You will know everything in this vlog.
So let's cut a little from here.
Come on brother, come on, come on, take it, take it, take it.
Rest I am seeing one thing in Hunter right now.  I am
noticing.
Its fuel is getting exhausted very quickly.
Meaning its mileage has almost ended.
Now I don't know why this is happening
?  If you know then please comment, the
comment section is absolutely open for you.   Please
comment and tell me why this is happening
and what could be done to
improve fuel economy.
I have already got it serviced.
So I don't hope that it
needs service because I have
its papers.  I will show you the papers
after some time when I
reach the service centre, if I have them then
I will definitely show them to you that I have already got it
serviced.
Now the service that is going to be provided for this is going to cost
₹10,000, about which I have
talked to my company people.   It
feels a little strange to do a little vogue in traffic because
you have to pay attention to the traffic and you also have to ride the bike.
So now the hustle is on to find a service center.
Let's see where the service centre is.
Firstly,
these people do not build service centres in such remote corners.
Service centres are not available in half the places.   I do
n't know where the service center is.
I can't even see the other street here.  Now
I asked someone where is the service centre
?  So he is telling that
brother, there is another street from here.  It is inside it.
Brother, please build the service centre a little outside like this.
If
anyone from Royal Enfield is looking at it, then it would be because it is
definitely a third party
vendor.
Third party vendors are the vendors who
take tenders.  Be it Royal Enfield or
any other.  Well, look here, there is such a small
board of Royal Enfield and
look, that is
inside it.
That is the Royal Enfield service centre.  Here it is.  Let's
see what process is there here and
what is not.
So right now we are outside the service center.
I just went inside.  I went inside and
talked to him and after talking I came to know
that their manager was not here today.
So now to submit the bike,
I will have to come here again tomorrow and
submit it and even after submitting it,
they are saying that brother, you will have to keep the bike with us for minimum 15 days
and that too a
separate job card for ex-accidental damage will be made
which will be made by the manager and
their manager is not here right now.  He is on leave today.
So let's see what the next process will be.
Whatever happens, I will shoot tomorrow's vlog and
show it to you.
So friends, this is what happens, you have
n't eaten or drunk anything, but the glass overflows.  What
I mean to say is that brother, we
leave home after thinking a lot about it that today we will do this
, today we will do that.  But then nothing happens in the end.  So why didn't it happen
?  Because his brother manager did not
come, my work also could not be done.  Otherwise, let's
submit it today and get the work done.   Let us
see what the next process is and
what it is not.
I am thinking that there is another service centre
in Chhatarpur, I should go there and deposit it.
So whatever happens, I will see what happens now.
So finally after
understanding everything and seeing everything, the final
conclusion is that we are going
home now.  I will go home and discuss
with my brother what to do and what
not to do because he has said that
brother, tomorrow his manager will come and talk to him,
then whatever conversation will happen, whatever discussion will happen,
then we will see that thing, I could
not record the conversation inside because
first of all they are not allowing me to
shoot with the camera, so that is why
I did not force him, so
whatever conversation I had, I have
told you as it is.  He has clearly
said that brother, you will have to
make a job card for accidental cover.
Ok?  He will get it made tomorrow.  Then
after that the most important thing is his manager.  So the
manager is on leave today.  So tomorrow his
manager will come at something like 10:00.  So we will
also come again at 10:00.  Then after that we will get the
job card made.  Then after that we will show you
brother that these things are damaged here and here
and further process has to be done to do these things.
So let's see which part will be changed, which will
not be changed or what
repair will be done.  Whatever happens, X and Z
will show you.   That was all
today's ride.  Now let's go home.
Well brother, I have used up all my fuel and the
work is still not done.  On top of that they are saying that
your car will remain parked
at the service centre for 15 days.  I agree
that it is okay.  A week or two.  That's
ok.  That is a
small matter.  But friend, 15 days have been
too much.
How will I live instead of my car for 15 days?   I have a
habit of riding daily.  But come on, I do
n't have any other
bikes, I have three of them.  So we will manage it.  Now I will
ride a small CC bike.  Higher
cc bike.  Come on, let's run it sometime.  We will
manage it in that only.  No problem.
So if you liked the video,
then like it, follow it and
subscribe.  Give a thumbs up.
Thank you all for watching my video.